[
  {"question":"What is eight times seven?", "answer":"56"},
  {"question":"What is eight times eight?", "answer":"64"},
  {"question":"What is eight times nine?", "answer":"72"},
  {"question":"What is eight times ten?", "answer":"80"},
  {"question":"What is eight times eleven?", "answer":"88"},
  {"question":"What is eight times twelve?", "answer":"96"},
  {"question":"What is nine times eight?", "answer":"72"},
  {"question":"What is nine times nine?", "answer":"81"},
  {"question":"What is nine times ten?", "answer":"90"},
  {"question":"What is nine times eleven?", "answer":"99"},
  {"question":"What is nine times twelve?", "answer":"108"},
  {"question":"What is ten times eight?", "answer":"80"},
  {"question":"What is ten times nine?", "answer":"90"},
  {"question":"What is ten times ten?", "answer":"100"},
  {"question":"What is ten times eleven?", "answer":"110"},
  {"question":"What is ten times twelve?", "answer":"120"},
  {"question":"What is eleven times seven?", "answer":"77"},
  {"question":"What is eleven times eight?", "answer":"88"},
  {"question":"What is eleven times nine?", "answer":"99"},
  {"question":"What is eleven times ten?", "answer":"110"},
  {"question":"What is eleven times six?", "answer":"66"}
]
